1. Write a program that asks the user for an integer number, then judge whether it is odd or even:
Enter an integer number : 45
The number is odd.

2. Programmìng Project 9 in Chapter 5 asked you to write a program that determines which of two dates comes earlier on the calendar. Generalize the program so that the user may enter any number of dates. The user will enter 0/0/0 to indicate that no more dates will be entered: 
   Enter a date (mm/dd/yy): 3/6/08
   Enter a date (mm/dd/yy): 5/17/07
   Enter a date (mm/dd/yy): 6/3/07
   Enter a date (mm/dd/yy): 0/0/0
   5/17/07 is the earliest date
